Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Visual Materials, 1962-2009
  - Subseries 2: Audio, 1965-2009
    - Jordanian Master (9 minutes), 1984 November 1; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 8)
    - Denver Symphony Show, Act I (56 minutes), 1985 October 12; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 9)
    - Denver Symphony Show, Cast A, Act II, 2nd Night (59 minutes), 1985 October 12; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 10)
    - Super Bowl XX Half Time analog safety copy (28 minutes), 1985 December 26; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 11)
    - Beat of the Future, commercially produced cassette tape (40 minutes), 1985; Audio cassette tape (Box 107, Item 12)
    - Coca Cola Tour/Japan (33 minutes), 1985-1986; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 13)
    - Coca Cola Tour/Japan without lead vocal (22 minutes), 1985-1986; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 14)
    - Japan Tour (songs with lead vocal) (22 minutes), 1985-1986; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 15)
    - USSR Moscow Cast A, Tape 1 of 4 (92 minutes), 1987; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 1)
    - USSR Moscow Cast A, Tape 3 of 4 (92 minutes), 1987; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 2)
    - USSR Moscow Cast A, Tape 4 of 4 (57 minutes), 1987; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 3)
    - GM Canada (13 minutes), 1988 February; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 4)
    - Poslovitsa (Russian Proverb Song) (9 minutes), 1988 May; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 5)
    - Chebatukha (Soviet dance) (9 minutes), 1988 May; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 6)
    - Rhythm of the World, commercially produced cassette album (47 minutes), 1991; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 7)
    - Joyco Productions, Up with People, Project Pride & Faith Christian Academy (5 minutes), 1994 March 7; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 8)
    - The Festival, commercially produced cassette album (54 minutes), 1995; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 9)
    - Japan (23 minutes), 1996; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 10)
    - Cast C ’96-’97 French= Festa, Buying It, Within Our Reach (10 minutes), 1996-1997; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 11)
    - Cast C ‘96-‘97 French Songs, Festa, Buying It, Within our Reach (56 minutes), 1996-1997; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 12)
    - Japan (23 minutes), 1997; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 13)
    - Japan (30 minutes), 1998; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 14)
    - Roads Backing Tracks Master Disc, Disc #2, 1998 July; CD disc (Box 108, Item 15)
    - Interlocken- Denver, CO (40 minutes), 1999 July 19; Audio cassette tape (Box 108, Item 16)
    - Japan (8 minutes), 1999; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 17)
    - World Tour, 2008-2009; CD disc (Box 108, Item 18)
    - Bob Hope Spots, cut 1 & 2, 30 seconds (1 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 108, Item 19)
    - “Favorites Album #1121-A”, Sides 1 & 2, ¼”, 15 ips, 2-track (37 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 1)
    - “Favorites Album #1121-B”, Sides 3 & 4, ¼”, 15 ips, 2-track (39 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 2)
    - Frank Fields, Children, Pace Records (6 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 3)
    - Fresh New Day dub master (21 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 4)
    - “Greyhound Album” Side 1 ¼”, 15 ips, 2-Track, original (22 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 5)
    - “Greyhound Album” Side 2 ¼”, 15 ips, 2-Track, original (21 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 6)
    - Hollywood Bowl tape 4 (10 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 7)
    - “Inaugural” (28 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 8)
    - “Inaugural” (9 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 9)
    - Leave Me a Dream or Two, Paul Colwell (3 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 10)
    - Leave Me a Dream, Paul Colwell (6 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 11)
    - McCormick has the Recipe (41 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 12)
    - Miss Zimmerman voice training exercises (27 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 13)
    - NASA Gemini Astronauts in flight, Reel “C” (35 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 14)
    - Operation Push Saturday Forum (2 CDs) (94 minutes), undated; Audio cassette tape (Box 109, Item 15)
    - Oscillators... Beat of the Future (1 minute), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 16)
    - Promotional Spots, Show for all Seasons, Tucson Symphony (13 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 109, Item 17)
    - A Show for All Seasons promotional spots 1-7 and 9-14 (15 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 1)
    - The Smithfields master for cutting masters (20 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 2)
    - The Smithfields 2 track master (32 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 3)
    - Sound element #2 for film, interviews San Manuel, roads shots (16 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 4)
    - Sound element #3 for film, interviews on bus, arrival in Tucson, wild sound (16 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 5)
    - Sound element #4 for film arrival-Tucson (3 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 6)
    - Sound element #5 for film 2nd Unit (17 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 7)
    - Spanish album, modified; Dolby A not decoded during migration, Dolby tone at tail (19 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 8)
    - Spanish Album #1128 Side 1 (18 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 9)
    - Spanish Album #1128 Side 2 (20 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 10)
    - Tom Sullivan “Childhood” versions 1 & 2 (9 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 11)
    - Tom Sullivan “Give the Children back” with 3 songs (11 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 12)
    - “UWP in Hollywood” 2-Track 15ips Protection copy (36 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 13)
    - “UWP in NYC” 2-Track ips Protection copy (36 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 14)
    - UWP Schick TV Sing out commercial audio album tape (48 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 15)
    - “Video Album” Toronto Tape 1 of 2 (36 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 16)
    - “Video Album” Toronto Tape 2 of 2 (36 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 17)
    - “Viva la Gente” in Mexico Pace Records Side II (10 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 18)
    - Viva la Gente Italian (34 minutes), undated; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 110, Item 19)
  - Subseries 3: Moving Images, 1965-2000
    This subseries contains film of Up with People event, performances and interviews. This subseries is arranged chronologically. Access copy DVDs are available. The migrated copies of these audio visual materials were transferred from the originals in 2012 and 2013.
    - Schick TV special, color, sound (55 minutes: 1980 feet), 1965; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 111, Item 1)
    - Schick Television special, telecine of 16mm film, poor image quality (56 minutes), 1965; 3/4” Umatic (Box 112, Item 1)
    - Sing out Speak out ’65 film (11 minutes: 396 feet), 1965; 16mm motion picture film (Box 112, Item 2)
    - Sing Out ’65 (3:37 minutes: 130 feet), 1965; 16mm motion picture film (Box 112, Item 3)
    - Sing Out ’65 Colwell clip, black and white, sound (4:54 minutes: 176 feet), 1965; 16mm motion picture film (Box 112, Item 4)
    - Moral Re-armament “Sing out Explosion” hosted by Pat Boone (55 minutes), 1966 December 18; 2” Quad NTSC Videotape (Box 113, Item 1)
    - Sing Out ’66 Charlotte, North Carolina Coliseum, kinescope Black and white, sound (64 minutes: 2304 feet), 1966; 16mm motion picture film (Box 114, Item 1)
    - Sing Out ‘66 print ZDF German silent (4:21 minutes: 156 feet), 1966; 16mm motion picture film (Box 115, Item 1)
    - USAF training film TF-6054c “Moral Leadership, Who are we” (33 minutes: 1188 feet), 1967; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 116, Item 1)
    - “UWP in Europe New Dimension” (22 minutes: 775 feet), 1969; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 117, Item 1)
    - Brad Davis Show, Cut: I’m Thinking WTIC-TV (2:50 minutes), 1970 April 18; 2” Quad (Box 118, Item 1)
    - London Early 70s (note severe perforation damage) (20 minutes: 730 Feet), 1970-1975; 16mm color (Box 118, Item 2)
    - CBS out takes- Bob Banner Association picture and mag sound (7 minutes: 252 feet), 1971-1972; 16mm color and magnetic film (Box 118, Item 3)
    - CBS out takes- Getting on a bus in Spain (2 minutes: 72 feet), 1971-1972; 16mm color (Box 118, Item 4)
    - Nebraska ETV, Cultural affairs (55 minutes), 1971 January 31; 2” Quad NTSC Videotape (Box 119, Item 1)
    - Up with People (60 minutes), 1973 June 1; 2” Quad PAL (Box 120, Item 1)
    - Carson & UWP Productions (30 minutes), 1973 October 1; 2” Quad NTSC Videotape (Box 121, Item 1)
    - CBS TV Spot- Up with People (45 minutes), 1973 October 2; 2” Quad NTSC (Box 122, Item 1)
    - "Multiversity" Interview with J. Blanton Belk & Hermann K. Bleibtreu- NBC TV (30 minutes), 1974 March 17; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 1)
    - Spokane Exposition (3 minutes), 1974; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 2)
    - UWP in Boston (33 minutes: 1197 feet), 1975; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 123, Item 3)
    - Up with People Cast C (110 minutes), 1975; DVD video (Box 123, Item 4)
    - Assembly University of Jacksonville (31 minutes), 1976 February; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 5)
    - UWP in Poland (33 minutes: 1188 feet), 1976; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 123, Item 6)
    - UWP in Poland (33 minutes), 1976; VHS videotape PAL (Box 123, Item 7)
    - China Reel One Genesis Concern (less than 20 minutes), 1978 July 21; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 8)
    - UWP segment “500” Queens Ball (22 minutes), 1978; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 9)
    - Florida governor Bob Graham with UWP cast (2 minutes), 1979 February 22; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 10)
    - "Scope" With Wally Shirra- KVOA TV Interview With Belk & Cast Performance (27 minutes), 1979; 3/4” Umatic (Box 123, Item 11)
    - Televisa special Cast C Mexico City (38 minutes), 1979; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 1)
    - Viva La Gente TV special #2/Spring, Mexico, (migrated to audio file since no video captured) (47 minutes), 1979; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 2)
    - Costa Rica Television Special 1980, Cassette #1 (62 minutes), 1980 August 5; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 3)
    - Costa Rica Television Special 1980, Cassette #2 (8 minutes), 1980 August 5; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 4)
    - San Antonia, Texas KENS-TV (28 minutes), 1980 September 15; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 5)
    - Italian TV Special, Cast C (22 minutes), 1980; 3/4” Umatic PAL (Box 124, Item 6)
    - Panama TV Special (41 minutes), 1980; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 7)
    - Super Bowl XIV, Edited master (bad sound) (30 minutes), 1980; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 8)
    - Zurich, Switzerland TV special, Cast C (32 minutes), 1980; 3/4” Umatic PAL (Box 124, Item 9)
    - Super Bowl XIV halftime, Pasadena WTBS “Nice People”, Atlanta highlights Boston Pops (30 minutes), 1980-1982; 3/4” Umatic (Box 124, Item 10)
    - UWP performance part 1 Mountain Bell (44 minutes), 1981 March 17; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 1)
    - UWP performance part 2 Mountain Bell (56 minutes), 1981 March 17; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 2)
    - Blanton Belk interview, WTVJ-TV Dade County/Miami, Florida (3 minutes), 1981 March 18; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 3)
    - Southern Bell (16 minutes), 1981 March 26; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 4)
    - Dodger Stadium (4 minutes), 1981 April 8; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 5)
    - Portugal TV special Cast E, Tape 1 of 2 (36 minutes), 1981 July 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 6)
    - Portugal TV special Cast E, Tape 2 of 2 (32 minutes), 1981 July 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 7)
    - Indianapolis 500 Cast D (28 minutes), 1981; 3/4” Umatic (Box 125, Item 8)
    - Sheridan, Wyoming, KSGW-TV Special (21 minutes), 1981; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 1)
    - Montana TV Special (30 minutes), 1982 December 18; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 2)
    - Promotion Super Bowl XVI (18 minutes), 1982; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 3)
    - Carolina Today Program, WIS-TV, Columbia, SC (27 minutes), 1983 April 6; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 4)
    - “Auf los Geht’s los” Special from German TV Cast D NTSC (14 minutes), 1983 April 13; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 5)
    - “Auf los Geht’s los” ARD-TV West Germany (15 minutes), 1983 May; 3/4” Umatic, PAL (Box 126, Item 6)
    - Cast C 1982-1983 Hagen, Germany ZDF TV Show (18 minutes), 1983 May 21; 1/2” VHS (Box 126, Item 7)
    - ZDF (German) TV special Reel II of II (14 minutes), 1983 May 21; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 8)
    - Visit with King and Queen Brewery-Alken, Belgium, get together Concentra produced by 18 18 Johan Van Overbeke, Concentra NV (60 minutes), 1983 November 11; 3/4” Umatic PAL (Box 126, Item 9)
    - Kronzucker interview, ZDF program (37 minutes), 1983 November 14; 3/4” Umatic, PAL (Box 126, Item 10)
    - Ontario/Buffalo, NY TV spot, 8411031 (2 minutes), 1983; 3/4” Umatic (Box 126, Item 11)
    - Master show excerpts revised (14 minutes), 1984 January 4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 1)
    - Pennsylvania Bell Opening Night Celebration “The Future Starts Today” part 1 show (60 minutes), 1984 January 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 2)
    - Pennsylvania Bell Opening Night Celebration “The Future Starts Today” part 2 show (60 minutes), 1984 January 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 3)
    - Interview with Roswitta Roensch, cast member (19 minutes), 1984 July 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 4)
    - Reader’s Digest, 8408033 (61 minutes), 1984 August; 1/2” VHS (Box 127, Item 5)
    - San Xavier Mission/ UWP offices DIT Eval meeting, 8408002 (13 minutes), 1984 August 2; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 6)
    - Tape #4, Arizona Ballroom (15 minutes), 1984 August 2; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 7)
    - Bruce Babbitt- Tape #1 Roger, Morning (15 minutes), 1984 August 9; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 8)
    - Governor Bruce Babbitt (14 minutes), 1984 August 9; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 9)
    - Eugene Cernan (40 minutes), 1984 August 11; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 10)
    - Jerash Festival dub of master final cut (12 minutes), 1984 August 17; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 11)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #1 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 12)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #2 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 127, Item 13)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #3 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 1)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #4 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 2)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #5 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 3)
    - Jerash Festival Tape #6 (30 minutes), 1984 September 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 4)
    - Arizona Illustrated, summer KUAT-TV (6 minutes), 1984; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 5)
    - Cast E Video Scrapbook (45 minutes), 1984; 3/4" PAL Umatic (Box 128, Item 6)
    - “Music and a Whole lot more” 2 promotional segments (13 minutes), 1984; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 7)
    - Rehearsal for Host Families Cast E (18 minutes), 1985 January 26; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 8)
    - Honeywell Centennial (24 minutes), 1985 April 1; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 9)
    - Up with People "Anaheim Convention Center" Video Series- Tapes 1 (60 minutes), 1985 June 1; 3/4” Umatic (Box 128, Item 10)
    - Up with People "Anaheim Convention Center" Video Series- Tapes 2 (49 minutes), 1985 June 1; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 1)
    - Up with People "Anaheim Convention Center" Video Series- Tapes 3 (12 minutes), 1985 June 1; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 2)
    - Wiesbaden, Germany "Cast B" (60 minutes), 1985 July 1; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 3)
    - Tom Sullivan tape 1 of 3 (19 minutes), 1985 August 12; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 4)
    - Tom Sullivan “Room for Everyone” tape 2 of 3 (18 minutes), 1985 August 12; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 5)
    - Tom Sullivan “We’ll be There” tape 3 of 3 (19 minutes), 1985 August 12; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 6)
    - “Auf los Geht’s los” Eurovision TV ARD (63 minutes), 1985 September; 3/4” Umatic, PAL (Box 129, Item 7)
    - Opening Session (56 minutes), 1985; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 8)
    - Cast E: Opening Session Amphitheatre High School, Tucson Tape 1 of 2 (19 minutes), 1986 January 15; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 9)
    - Cast E: Opening Session Amphitheatre High School, Tucson Tape 2 of 2 (19 minutes), 1986 January 15; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 10)
    - Cast B Dusseldorf Erkrath (32 minutes), 1986 May 2; 3/4” Umatic (Box 129, Item 11)
    - Luxembourg Cast D (23 minutes), 1986 July 30; VHS videotape (Box 129, Item 12)
    - Cast E Quebec, Canada (103 minutes), 1986 August 15; VHS videotape (Box 130, Item 1)
    - Window Rock #1, Cast C (20 minutes), 1986 September 2-4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 2)
    - Window Rock #2, Cast C (20 minutes), 1986 September 2-4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 3)
    - Window Rock #3, Cast C, (17 minutes), 1986 September 2-4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 4)
    - Window Rock #4, Cast C (15 minutes), 1986 September 2-4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 5)
    - Window Rock #5, Cast C (21 minutes), 1986 September 2-4; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 6)
    - UWP segment- March of Dimes (13 minutes), 1986; VHS videotape (Box 130, Item 7)
    - Super Bowl XX, Sydney, Australia Rugby Finals, Stockholm-Hockey Championship (43 minutes), 1986; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 8)
    - Super Bowl ‘86 half time show rehearsals, Belgium, Hawaii, China (64 minutes), 1986; 1” Type C videotape (Box 130, Item 9)
    - Super Bowl ‘86 half time show rehearsals version 2, Bruges, Belgium- cast D, Honolulu- cast A (18 minutes), 1986; 3/4” Umatic (Box 130, Item 10)
    - TV 2 Finland Cast C Tape #2 (32 minutes), 1986; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 1)
    - Cast A in Belgium (Flemish TV), Cast C (Dutch TV) (9 minutes), 1986-1987; 3/4” Umatic PAL (Box 131, Item 2)
    - Cast B Indianapolis 1986-1987, Opening ceremonies NBC (4 minutes), 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 3)
    - Highlights video revised (21 minutes), 1986-1987; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 4)
    - Cast E, Amphitheatre HS 1st half (58 minutes), 1987 March 7; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 5)
    - Channel 13 night cast (Tucson) KOLD-TV, Cast E (3 minutes), 1987 March 26-27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 6)
    - KPRC-TV Houston “The Kid Show” segment Cast D (15 minutes), 1987 April; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 7)
    - Sing out Reunion, poor video quality (71 minutes), 1987 June 2; VHS videotape (Box 131, Item 8)
    - Sound assembly International Special Olympics Cast E tape 1 of 3 (20 minutes), 1987 August 5; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 9)
    - Cast comments and closing ceremonies International Special Olympics Cast E tape 2 of 3 (18 minutes), 1987 August 5 and August 7; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 10)
    - Closing ceremonies International Special Olympics Cast E tape 3 of 3 (19 minutes), 1987 August 7; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 11)
    - Performance on US Navy ship Cast B (11 minutes), 1987 December 10; 3/4” Umatic (Box 131, Item 12)
    - Cast E Ballet Folklorico de Mexico (49 minutes), 1987; 3/4” Umatic (Box 132, Item 1)
    - International Special Olympics (2 minutes), 1987; 1/2” VHS (Box 132, Item 2)
    - Cast E opening day tape 3 of 3 (20 minutes), 1988 January 9; 3/4” Umatic (Box 132, Item 3)
    - Russia (Finland) Helsinki “Duck Tape” (20 minutes), 1988 June 4; Betacam (Box 132, Item 4)
    - Cast Interviews Tape 5B Lapeenranta, 023 (6 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam SP (Box 132, Item 5)
    - Cast Interviews Tape 3B Lapeenranta, 024 (21 minutes), June 6, 1988; Betacam SP (Box 132, Item 6)
    - Cast Interviews Tape 2B Lapeenranta, 025 (21 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam SP (Box 132, Item 7)
    - Cast Interviews Lapeenranta, 026 (21 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam SP (Box 132, Item 8)
    - Finland 1A Lappeenranta rehearsal B roll (20 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam (Box 132, Item 9)
    - Finland 2A Lappeenranta rehearsal B roll (17 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam (Box 132, Item 10)
    - C exercise B roll 6/6/88 Russia- 1B Intvu- Lapeenranta exercise b roll (17 minutes), 1988 June 6; Betacam (Box 132, Item 11)
    - Russia 4A Leningrad dinner- dancing (6 minutes), 1988 June 7; Betacam (Box 132, Item 12)
    - Russia B6 Leningrad dinner (7 minutes), 1988 June 7; Betacam (Box 132, Item 13)
    - Russia 5A Leningrad Veteran’s Memorial (20 minutes), 1988 June 8; Betacam (Box 132, Item 14)
    - Russia 7A Leningrad conservatory (20 minutes), 1988 June 8; Betacam (Box 132, Item 15)
    - Russia 7B Leningrad Veteran’s Memorial camera B (20 minutes), 1988 June 8; Betacam (Box 132, Item 16)
    - Russia 8A Leningrad conservatory, family home (20 minutes), 1988 June 8; Betacam (Box 132, Item 17)
    - Russia 9A Leningrad beauty shots (13 minutes), 1988 June 8; Betacam (Box 132, Item 18)
    - Russia 10A-I Performance in park (20 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 132, Item 19)
    - Russia 10A-II Performance in park continued (13 minutes), 1988x June 9; Betacam (Box 132, Item 20)
    - Russia 11A Leningrad, park footage, Ross et al (10 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 1)
    - Russia 13A Leningrad (12 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 2)
    - Russia 14A Leningrad (12 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 3)
    - Russia 15A Leningrad performance (18 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 4)
    - Russia 16A Leningrad performance (19 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 5)
    - Russia 17A Leningrad and backstage (20 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 6)
    - Russia Leningrad Concert, 029 (21 minutes), June 9, 1988; Betacam SP (Box 133, Item 7)
    - Russia B9 Leningrad Children’s Hospital (20 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 8)
    - Russia C3 Leningrad concert, stereo house feed (15 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 9)
    - Russia Leningrad concert C1 machine, house feed stereo (21 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 10)
    - Russia 1B Leningrad performance (17 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 11)
    - Russia 2B Camera B, Leningrad performance (21 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 12)
    - Russia 3B Leningrad performance (12 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 13)
    - Russia B Leningrad Children’s Hospital (20 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 14)
    - Russia Leningrad beauty shots (12 minutes), 1988 June 9; Betacam (Box 133, Item 15)
    - Russia B Arrival at Kalinin, rally (19 minutes), 1988 June 10; Betacam (Box 133, Item 16)
    - Russia leaving Leningrad ceremony camera B (20 minutes), 1988 June 10; Betacam (Box 133, Item 17)
    - Russia 18A Kalinin Peace demo (20 minutes), 1988 June 11; Betacam (Box 133, Item 18)
    - Russia 19A Kalinin Peace/body builders (20 minutes), 1988 June 11; Betacam (Box 133, Item 19)
    - Russia Kalinin peace march (20 minutes), 1988 June 11; Betacam (Box 133, Item 20)
    - Russia 20A, Sports show Kalinin (16 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 133, Item 21)
    - Russia 21A Kalinin church and park (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 1)
    - Russia 22A Kalinin rehearsal (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 2)
    - Russia 23A Kalinin performance (14 minutes), June 12, 1988; Betacam (Box 134, Item 3)
    - Russia 23A Kalinin performance stop and gos cam A (21 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 4)